真爱字幕组
竭诚奉献
翻译：
Livia  江米球
Dwyer  Sincity
翻译：
飞越无限  微云
压制&校对：飞越无限
早上好 威廉姆
Good morning, William.
早上好 布洛克先生
Good morning, Mr Bullock.
允许你早上喝点咖啡了么?
Are you sometimes permitted coffee?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
那就来三分之一杯?
About a third of a cup?
然后倒满牛奶
Completed with cow's milk.
糖怎么放?
As to sugar...
三勺吗
three spoons?
威廉姆 你有没有想象过 也是这样的早上
Is this the morning, William, do you suppose...
这盏灯的尖顶像印第安矛一样
the tip of this lamp, like an lndian spear,
刺入我的头顶
goes into the top of my head?
我没想过  先生
I don't know, sir.
这口味比得上你母亲做的吗?
Does it stand comparison with your mother's?
比不上 先生
No, sir.
要再加块方糖吗
Stiffened with a further lace of sugar?
我是说我父亲的做的更好 先生
I mean that he would make it, sir.
我父亲会冲咖啡
My father would.
你有时间小坐一会儿吗?
Do you have time to sit a bit?
我想我有空 因为昨晚把柴劈了
I suppose I might do, having chopped the kindling last evening.
威廉姆 你能给我讲讲你父亲吗
Would you tell me about your father, William?
作为他弟弟我并没有你这么多机会了解他
I didn't know my brother so well as you had a chance to.
罗伯特离开的时候我才9岁
I was nine when Robert left our home.
我想你有更多时间了解他
I think you knew him longer.
你当时已经11岁了
You were 11.
我很了解他
I knew him pretty well.
那他最喜欢做什么呢?
What did he like doing best?
有时他会唱歌
Sometimes he'd sing.
但不是军歌 是其它类型的
Not army songs, but other kinds.
他会让母亲笑
He'd make Mother laugh.
他学野鸭叫比别人都好听
He made the best duck calls of anyone.
他会邮购木制品
He would send away for the wood...
他还教我反击
and he taught me comebacks
还有学饲养员呼叫
and feeder calls and hails.
乌特先生和我得去营地看看
Mr Utter and l have some camp business to see to.
威廉姆  你很会学鸭叫吗
William...are you a good duck caller?
我想是的  我可以示范给你看  先生
I suppose I'm pretty good. I could show you, sir.
我知道Belle Fourche路上有些壶洞
I know of some potholes over Belle Fourche way...
那些洞很好捕鸭子
that are pretty good for ducks.
好的  先生
All right, sir.
再见  布洛克先生
Goodbye, Mr Bullock.
E.b. 法纳姆  Al
E.B. Farnum, Al.
进来  E.B.
Come in, E.B.!
我已经被这该死的牙痛折磨完了
I've been prostrated by the agonies of the damned.
而我们就要被审判了
Judgement is up on us then.
一颗臼齿都烂掉了
A molar rotted through.
我也很苦恼 毕竟你是我的耳目
Distressing me also, that you are my eyes and ears...
而多事之秋的昨天你居然身体不适
and a day as eventful as yesterday should find you indisposed.
知道我被想念了  多少有点安慰
Some solace in knowing I'm missed.
你错过了他妈的电报员的到来
You missed the advent of the fucking telegraph operator...
而你本应将他领到你的客房里
that had you steered into one of your rooms...
从此以后你就能贴身监视他了
you could have kept tabs on henceforth.
真是疼得我要命
The pain nearly killed me.
只要你还有一口气在
As you still breathe amongst us...
我就会让你去和那该死的俄国人交朋友去
I shall ask you to befriend this fucking Russian.
-俄国人?  -就是那电报员 E.B
-Russian? -The fucking telegraph operator, E.B...
他妈的是俄国人
is a fucking Russian.
我当然会去亲近他 我很喜欢俄国人
Of course I'll befriend him. I'm very fond of Russians.
而当你们之间的信任加深时
And as the trust between you deepens...
我们将对来往于扬克顿的电报消息特别感兴趣
we'll be particularly interested in messages to and from Yankton.
谁啊?
Yeah?
打扰一下  E.B.
Sorry, E.B.
Al  你也许想看看那个
Al, you might wanna take a gander at that.
E.B.马上要走了  你不会错过他的
E.B. is leaving. You won't miss him.
他住在梅里克家  而且看起来像狂欢节的奖品
He's living at Merrick's and looks like the prize at a carnival.
我临走看到的场面是多么的令人愉快啊!
What a delightful image to carry away with me!
斯维尔根将梅里克这张牌打出来
Swearengen's put the paperman's boat
说的全是胡言论语
to sea with a hold full of fucking bullshit.
-他想多要五千美元  -天呐!
-He wants $5,000 more upstairs. -Jesus Christ!
告诉那个死胖子让他亲自下来拿
Tell that fat bastard he can come down and get it hisself.
他说如果我带上去就再付100美元
He says it's $100 if I bring it up.
Tess 你已经拿给他的5000美元
Is the $5,000 you already brought him
难道就已经使用了吗?
in any kind of action, Tess?
那钱只是为了给他干你的时候看的
It's just for him to look at while he fucks you!
所以...Tess 我是不是要从他付的9美元里
So... do I want my $8, Tess,
拿到我的8美元
of the $9 he pays for the fuck...
还是作为你给他拿钱的小费的
and my $90 of the $100 he gives you to
一百美元中的九十美元?
bring it up to him...
还是说如果他亲自下来再拿五千美元
or do I want to give fat boy the opportunity...
应该给胖子个机会
if he has to come down to get the other $5,000...
来试试他的运气?
to test his luck on the floor here amongst the games of chance?
我明白了
I see.
[这段话的意思是已经给了曼纽尔5000块，他再要500块
儿托利维想利用赌博拿回第一次付出的5000块]
亲爱的 别误会了我
And don't mistake me, honey.
我是想花时间解释给你听
I want to take the time to explain myself to you.
我们来见见摩斯·曼纽尔谈谈关于他哥哥被枪击的事
We've come to see Mose Manuel about his brother getting shot.
Tess 把摩斯·曼纽尔叫下来
Fetch Mose Manuel, Tess.
告诉他
Tell him...
警长布洛克想在这赌场给予些许慰问
Sheriff Bullock wants to pay his condolences here amongst the games of chance.
警长  你身边谣言四起
All these rumours, Sheriff, swirling around you.
你怎么还能撑得住气?
How do you keep your hat on?
如果你同意 你在这签字
If you'll sign right here,
女士 就是在这角落写上A.G.
ma'am. And give us a A.G. in the corner.
是那种金融交易中艺术字眼的缩写吗
Is that abbreviation a term of art in financial transactions?
应该让我知道这缩写的含义吧?
Ought I acquaint myself with its meaning?
女士  A.G.是您名字首字母的缩写
That abbreviation, ma'am, is your initials.
若我我再问我已签署了接收的那些钱在哪里
And by asking the whereabouts of the currency I signed for receiving...
是不是显得更愚昧无知了?
do I reveal an even deeper stupidity?
在从丹佛来的大马车上今天应该会到
The coach from Denver should get in today.
那我们买的用来放在即将建造的银行里的保险箱呢？
And the safe we've purchased to be housed in the bank we're to build?
它也在大马车里
It's inside the coach as well.
保险箱躺在马车里
Safe's inside the coach...
而您的钱躺在保险箱里 这就是全部了
and the currency is inside the safe is the full picture.
-那我确实愚昧了  -没有  女士
-There, I did manage to be stupid. -No, ma'am.
那你要在斯塔尔和布洛克五金店
And you will see to the safe's temporary situation...
留心保险箱的暂时情况了
at the Star & Bullock Hardware Store?
是的  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
你的注意力应从如此的尴尬情形移开
Gaze averted from the awkwardness such a situation generates.
集中在保护你钱财的增长上
Fixing my eyes instead on its pluses securing your money.
好极了  埃尔斯沃斯先生
Excellent then, Mr Ellsworth.
我能再麻烦你帮我送下这封信么？
May I further impose on you to convey this letter?
当然可以
Of course.
给斯维尔根先生？
Mr Swearengen?
麻烦了
Please!
没事的
All right.
还有什么事我们要讨论么？
Is there anything else for us to discuss?
此时不适合
Not at this time.
那我就离开了
I'll be going then.
-谁？  -琼妮·斯塔布斯
-Who's that? -It's Joanie Stubbs.
你在我门外干什么
You're outside my place.
出事之后继续我的不称职的警卫工作
Keeping half-assed vigil after the fact.
Well  进来告诉我你在说什么
Well, come in and tell me what you mean.
不了  那就没事了
No, that's all right.
那个你跟我提到的混蛋
That cocksucker you spoke to me of...
昨晚一脸鲜血的从这儿走了
come from here last night with a bloody fucking mug.
-我打得  -好的
-I gave it to him. -Good.
不管怎样  被枪指着 他告诉我
Anyways, he told me at rifle point...
你没事
you was okay.
-我是没事  -我知道如果他说谎了你就已经死了
-I am. -I knew if he was lying you was dead...
我也害怕你死在夜里
and feared finding you so in the darkness.
从我很小的时候就很害怕那样
Scared that way since I was small.
Well  进来吧  珍
-Well, come on in, Jane.
我又想到  要是你还活着  为什么我还要敲门呢
If you was alive, why fucking knock was my thinking.
打扰了你入睡
Interfere with you getting to sleep...
-或者你已经睡着了  -珍  外面冻的我屁股疼
-or being asleep already-- -Jane, it's nippy on my twat.
那好了  再见了
All right then, see you later!
你还记得昨天你在里面么？
Do you remember you were in here yesterday?
是的 我记得
Yes, I fucking remember.
Well  那为啥不再进来了呢
Well, why not come in again?
也许我真的可以
Maybe I just fucking might.
Hey, hey, hey.
尼戈·杰纳勒尔牵了一匹野马
Nigger General's got a wild horse on his hands.
我很同情这匹没人性的畜生
I pity the brute beast who
它把它的的聪明都用在了和
pits his cunning against
尼戈·杰纳勒尔的智慧的较量上[结果它还没拼过]
the Nigger General's!
Oh, shit!
我们能在那个骑兵去南方之前
We can catch the cavalry
追上那个他  以100块的价格卖给他
before they head south and sell him for $100!
但是他们都要把马阉割了
But they want their horses cut.
你从哪抓到的它？
Where'd you catch him?
在一个箱形峡谷里我在它后面圈了个绳子栅栏
I sprung a rope fence behind him in a box canyon.
它逃离了苏族  但是他途经了一匹母马
He'd escaped the Sioux, but his path crossed an in-season mare's.
现在我可以阉割他  但是
Now I can nut him, but the
时间不对  他得遭罪
moon is wrong and he's gonna take it badly.
擦  我不会为了
Fuck, I ain't losing my
等个合适的月份而失去我赚100块钱的机会的
chance at $100 waiting on no fucking moon!
Okay  把你的手放这儿  好的
Okay. Here, put your hands right here, okay.
Hey  拜托
Hey! Come on.
清洗一下他就不会溃烂了
Wash him so he won't fester.
Hey  我来给它洗
-Hey, I got him.
好的  过来  孩子  过来
All right. Come here, boy. Come here.
Now  如果你想发泄在谁身上
Now, if you want to take it out on someone...
就记住是某个黑皮肤的白人阉割的你
remember it was very dark-skinned white folks that cut on you.
他们只是听起来像卖了你的黑人
They just sounded like niggers to throw you off.
这个字母是 D
This one's a "D."
这个是G
And this one's a "G."
第一个是什么
And what's the first one?
D？
"D"?
警长布洛克拒绝对传闻发表评论
"Sheriff Bullock declines comment on the swirl of rumours...
即与海伦娜的会晤  且二人有着长久的联系
"That parties in Helena with whom he has had long association...
后者对将营地并入
"Are keenly interested in
蒙大拿州有个极高的兴致
annexing our camp to the Montana territories.
先锋报也获悉
""The Pioneer also learns
怀俄明州方面的兴致
of interests more developed and advanced...
也更加的浓厚
"On the part of Wyoming."
你知道的夏延也会听说这个消息
You knew Cheyenne would be heard from.
别他妈坐在台阶上
Get the fuck up off them steps!
这里是忙碌的地方
Here's where it gets really fucking busy.
由华盛顿的匿名人士
"And of an offer secretly
秘密提供的提议中
proffered by certain elements in Washington, D.C...
要将我们的这些宝贝黑山并入美国
"To annex to America these our beloved hills...
作为一个独立的区域
"As a separate freestanding territory...
密切关注最终的州状态
"With an eye towards eventual statehood."
将朽木镇建成总部吧
Making Deadwood fucking headquarters.
强尼  别恰好在这儿瞎插嘴
Don't spread your legs for them just yet, Johnny.
否则不只墨西哥连法兰西都能知道了
Not with Mexico to be heard from and fucking France.
瞧瞧
There!
绅士们  加印了100份
One hundred extra copies, gentlemen...
以防我认为可能会出现
to satisfy the widened
今天报纸供不应求的局面
interest I expect today's edition may generate.
好极了  布拉萨诺夫先生  多印了100份
Wonderful, eh, Mr Blasanov? One hundred copies extra.
好吧
Okay.
我们出去溜达溜达？ 我的美国和俄国朋友？
Shall we walk a bit, my American and Russian friends?
去么？
Shall we?
我不能离开我的设备
I can't leave my apparatus.
我们都不能离开的  布拉萨诺夫
Are not all of us, Mr Blasanov,
多多少少都被我们的工作拴住了
tethered in some sense to our labours?
而有时候我们的生活
And at some point in our lives...
又不能容忍这种牵绊
is not acceptance of that tethering...
就要发现一种作乐的途径
discovery of a path to joy?
我也不太清楚  先生
Don't know, Mister--
凭良心说  难道牵制住我们的的认知
And does not the very knowing we are tethered allow us...
不允许我们不时地
in conscience upon occasion,
搞一些暂时的恢复性的乐事
the rejuvenating pleasures of respite?
那你自己去吧  A·W·梅里克
Take your walk alone, A.W.
我不去是因为
For I confess I'm mesmerised
我得承认我被布拉萨诺夫先生的机器迷住了
by Mr Blasanov's machine...
希望他可以解释一下它的工作方式
and hope he may explain its workings.
-Al看过先锋报了么？  -我不知道
-Has Al seen The Pioneer? -I don't know.
你自己问去
A mystery you should seek to solve.
-日安 -日安 女士
-Good day. -Good day, miss.
朽木镇先锋报的A·W·梅里克
A.W. Merrick of The Deadwood Pioneer.
- 我想发一份电报  -发电报  没问题
-I wish to send a telegram. -A telegram. Yes, of course.
那你去找那边的布拉萨诺夫先生
Then that's Mr Blasanov there you seek.
你好  我是布拉萨诺夫
How do you do? Blasanov.
黑山夏延电报公司职员
Cheyenne and Black Hills Telegraph Company.
你好
How do you do?
-伊斯林豪瑟女士  -法纳姆先生
-Miss lsringhausen. -Mr Farnum.
我想将这份消息发送出去
I wish this message sent.
好的
Oh, of course.
这有份表格需要你填一下
I have a form for you to write on. Please.
看来你并不对布拉萨诺夫先生的器械感到惊讶
You seem uncowed by Mr Blasanov's apparatus.
- 你是第一次见识它的神秘吗 -滚开
-Are you initiate in its mysteries? -Fuck off.
请坐
Please.
先生们
Ah, gentlemen!
有什么新闻
What news?
这个可怜的破报
This ink-stained wretch
只付印了100多份报纸
has just produced an overrun of 1 00 copies.
丹 你不觉得
Dan, don't you agree that the truth...
只要咬一口就必须要矫正每一个错误
if only a pinch, must season every falsehood,
或者味觉的错误判断
or the palate fucking rebels?
新手厨师不是也得
And mustn't the novice chef
注意着不舀出调料来
be mindful not to ladle out his concoction...
留下没加调料的部分
by the unseasoned fucking ton,
在他完善自己的作品之前
lest before he perfect his art...
以免他失去自己的顾客
he lose his clientele?
我希望能快点进球
I'd like the ball scores a little more fucking prompt.
抱歉
Excuse me.
艾尔·斯维尔根 我是你的话就不会进那间办公室
Al Swearengen, I would not go into that office if I were you.
你他妈的是三岁小孩吗
Were you fucking born yesterday?
不 先生 我不是三岁小孩
No, sir, I was not. I was not born yesterday!
那我们能像成年人一样谈话吗
Then may we please have a conversation as fucking adults?
再好不过
I think we'd better!
我不等了
I ain't waiting.
把这个交给他
Give this to him.
转告他不论内容是什么  都不要为难送信人
Tell him whatever its import, he'd best not serve the sender ill.
他和梅里克在一起  E.B.
He's in with Merrick, E.B.
我听到了不想等的消息
I bear news that don't want to wait.
你文章中造的每一个谣言  梅里克
Every rumour you floated in your article, Merrick...
我都认为是这个营地生存下去的可能性
I believe is a living possibility for this camp...
希望你将这话当做是我对你的奉承
and I want you to fucking hear that as a compliment.
这可是我从你嘴里听到的第一句奉承话
If so, it's the first from your lips.
因为那些可能性
Because all them possibilities
称为是接近于既成事实
called next to accomplished fact...
即使是一点抱怨也会让人们看出苗头
in one fucking outgush makes people smell a rat.
没错 我想是这样
Yes, I suppose so.
那些跟着我们的利益集团是粗暴的  梅里克
These interests coming after us, Merrick, they're fucking rough.
他们尾随着我们
They're going after our nuts.
他们是虚伪的混蛋
They're hypocrite cocksuckers.
说谎的战略和工具
And the fucking lying tactics and instruments...
他们用来摧毁与之为敌的人们
they use to fuck people up the ass can be turned against them.
我的报纸就是这样的工具
My newspaper being such an instrument.
但也要看规模 数量 比例 和趣味
But scale, amount, proportion, seasoning.
再喝一杯  梅里克
Drink that fucking second shot, Merrick!
我喜欢烈酒
I like my fucking liquor.
这点让我过早地在你身上看到了希望
A trait in you that gave me early hope.
我也喜欢墨臭味儿
I like stinking of fucking ink, too.
-闻一下 Al  -不
-Give it a fucking smell, Al. -No.
你写破文章是乐在其中 是吗
So you enjoyed writing your fucking article, huh?
度过夜晚的糟糕方式
Worse ways to spend a night,
将精力都浪费在一个烂想法上
putting shoulder to a fucking idea.
很明显  我付出的不止那些
Evidently, I put mine to over many.
绕了这么多弯子
Pursued down over many avenues.
营地的利益才是正题
The camp's welfare was the main idea.
Al
Al!
发现了些可疑的事情  需要你主张
Something strange has transpired I need you to construe.
什么事
What?
-当我  -进来
-As I was-- -Come in!
正当我和俄国电报员笼络交情的时候
As I was befriending the Russian operator...
那个女家庭教师来发电报了
that woman tutor came to send a telegram.
在我们寒暄的时候 我瞄见了电报的内容
We jockeyed a bit as I sought a glance at its contents...
最后 她喊了很多话
and finally, she shouted in so many words...
这是作为家庭教师的奇怪之处
and here is the strangeness in a tutor...
不符合她的的身份
to get the fuck away from her.
这个会议的秘密部分
Since the private part
已经结束了  埃尔斯沃斯带来的
of this meeting's over, Ellsworth brung it.
-说这么多话  -那个家教现在在哪
-ln so many words. -Where's the tutor now?
还和电报员在一起
Still with the operator,
显然还在等电报回信
apparently waiting for an answer to her message.
从前门离开吧
Leave by the front entrance.
回去前先散几分钟的步
Walk around for a few minutes before you go back to your place.
把那个家教带来  还有那个俄国人
Bring that tutor up here. The Russian, too.
看起来你是想捋清事情
It felt like something you'd want to construe.
-走开 E.B  -好 当然
-Go away, E.B. -All right. Certainly.
这是我们在奎特曼的边界贸易站买的向日葵种子
It's the seeds from the sunflower we had in Fort Quitman.
我保存在罐子里了 但罐子破了 种子被老鼠吃掉了
Which I had in a jar which broke and mice ate most of.
所以我只剩下三颗了
So now I only have these three.
我不知道你还带来了
I didn't know you brought them.
布洛克先生想念爸爸了
Mr Bullock's been missing Father.
今天早上我和他谈过了
I talked to him about it this morning.
既然爸爸喜欢向日葵  我想布洛克应该也一样
As Papa liked the sunflower, I thought Mr Bullock might as well.
我们一起种吧
Then shall we plant those together?
把土拍实了  我去拿水壶
Press the soil firmly on them, while I get the watering can.
也许我们应该和布洛克先生在他的商店共进午餐
Maybe we should take Mr Bullock lunch at his store.
我只知道意外降临在了我哥哥身上
An accident befell my brother is the sum of what I know...
我选择说出来你们该感到高兴
and be glad I choose to say it.
在纳托尔十号住宅  是他自己枪击吗
Gutshot, at Nuttall's Number 10, by his own hand?
没错
Correct.
你们卖了所有权那天你们两个还在一起吗
The day you sell out the claim you two were partnered on?
没错  去你的
Correct, and fuck yourself.
别一副胸有成竹的吊样
And don't act entitled to answers.
为什么查理要摆弄枪支？
Why was Charlie handling the gun?
去你妈的，别一副拽样
Fuck yourself, and don't act entitled.
为何当初你俩没看到纳托尔骑单车？
Why weren't you two watching Nuttall's bike ride?
去死吧
Fuck yourself.
我想看看他的枪和他的尸体
I want to see his gun and his remains.
查理被埋在哪了?
Where is Charlie buried?
我兄弟...
My brother...
就埋在一个秘密的地方
is buried in a secret burial place...
这是他自己的意愿
by his own private instructions!
天哪，布洛克! 要么就召集个法庭要么就别管了
Jesus Christ, Bullock! Put together a court or don't!
-安静点！ -别在我的地盘让我安静
-Quiet, you! -Don't hush me in my own fucking joint.
要是我们俩出去的话，老家伙...
And if we take it outside, old man...
会有一个和那天不同的结果的
expect a different outcome from the other fucking day.
你最好有五个
You best have five of your
准备好来福枪的帮手
fucking cappers then with rifles at the ready.
我有五个，五个人在他们身后，分散在屋里屋外。
I got five and five behind them, indoors or out.
我也是，咱得向警长报告伤亡情况...
I, too, must report to the Sheriff a death...
有一个康沃尔人在盗窃赫斯特的金矿时开枪击中了
a Cornishman at theft has been shot in Mr Hearst's claim.
挂了么？恩，挂了。
-Killed? -Yes, in flight.
这他妈的都是融合与资本，沃尔科特,你说对么？
It's all fucking amalgamation and capital, ain't it, Wolcott?
乌特先生，你是休姆的学生么？[一位哲学家]
Mr Utter, are you a student of Hume?
史密斯?卡尔马克思的门徒之一？-算了吧，查理.
-Smith? A disciple of Karl Marx? -Come on, Charlie.
我的雇主赫斯特先生，他在
My employer, Mr Hearst, has
蒙大拿地区可是有利益和人脉的，警长...
interests and connections in Montana, Sheriff...
今早的先锋报将风头转嫁给你了
as are imputed to you in this morning's Pioneer.
-你他妈的闭嘴！ -把他带出来！
-You shut your fucking mouth! -Get him out of here!
下来，查理!
Down, Charlie!
看来他抓住你把柄了，是吧摩斯?
Sure got to you, didn't he, Mose?
现在他要致你于死地了！
Now he's got to get you to die!
算了吧，查理!
Come on, Charlie!
让我呃...
Let me...
把我的手从这里伸过来，这样我就能...
get my arm through here so I can...
吃到我的吐司了。
secure my toast.
你一次又一次的抱住了我
You're gonna lift me one time too fucking many!
要是我让你离开的话，你就回不来了
You don't go back in there if I let you go.
-我要离开这该死的营地！-要去哪？
-I'm leaving the whole fucking camp! -Going where?
刚到手一封信 需要去比尔老婆那一趟。
A letter come to hand I need to take to Bill's missus.
哦 借个过。
Excuse me.
抱歉。谈点营地事务
Excuse me. Camp business.
-这是他死前写的。-我明白了
-He wrote just before he got killed. -I see.
你知道这他娘的是谁交给我的么？
And you know who fucking give it to me?
生活太疯狂了
How crazy life got?
钱肯定是给了这群人他们想要的东西
And money must buy these bastards any fucking thing they want!
里面的那个混蛋  合并&资本先生
That cocksucker inside, Mr Amalgamation & fucking Capital!
是赫斯特的地质学家给你的这封信么？
Hearst's geologist gave you the letter?
天知道他收买了谁
And God knows who he fucking bought it off of.
天知道这里有多少黑幕。
Or how many hands it passed through.
这他妈让我想到比尔的老婆
It fucks me up thinking Bill's missus...
要处理的东西却被那个混蛋碰过了。
got to handle something that cocksucker touched.
信里提到那天你揍他那事儿了吗
Was it over the letter you beat him the other day?
没，没。
No, no.
抱歉。
Excuse me.
不，我保证这事儿不算完
No, I give my word not to say what that was over.
我最好走开吧。
I'd best go.
以免联合&资本先生
Lest Mr Amalgamation &
想到什么
Capital takes one through the fucking head.
你那么讲是什么意思
What's the import of that expression?
我看起来像知道的么？
Do I look like I'd fucking know?
一些东部知名杂志社采访比尔的时候说过...
Some big shot eastern magazine reporter interviewing Bill said...
那会改变世界的
that was what's changing things around.
看看珍.我都不知道她会出什么事。
Jane. I don't know what's gonna come of fucking Jane.
我会留意她的。
I'll keep an eye on her.
你真应该把她关起来，别再让她酗酒了！
You should lock her in that cell and don't let her fucking drink!
摩斯·曼纽尔这事儿上出岔子了。
And don't fuck yourself up over Mose Manuel.
他说不定要被摆一道...
He'll get hisself fleeced of what's rightfully his...
这可会要了他的命。
and what he got by fucking murder.
他自己也会上审判台的。
He'll be judge on hisself and jury, too.
就他妈的跟我们这帮人一样。
Just like the fucking most of us.
这是丹佛过来的马车。
Coach from Denver.
有人找你来了。
Here's yours.
祝你好运，查理!
Good luck, Charlie!
我们给你和斯塔尔先生带了午餐。
We've brought you and Mr Star lunch.
谢了。
Thank you.
我醒啦！
I'm up!
你想洗个澡么？
You want the bath?
可能吧。
I may well get to that.
-这里很宽敞舒适，对不？-是啊。
-Ample here, ain't it? -Yeah.
这原来是个制桶作坊
Formerly a cooperage.
买下的人是我朋友埃迪
My friend Eddie that bought him out...
他说原来的雇主也才买了一个仨月。
said the man had been a season ahead of himself.
哇，作为妓院修理的很漂亮
Well, lovely as it's fixed as a brothel...
我期待你让它尽早重新开张。
I expect you will reopen soon enough.
广招人才，重新开张。
Restock and reopen.
你是这么想的，对么？
You'd think so, wouldn't you?
留下来吧，珍.
Stay awhile, Jane.
当我的座上宾。
Be my guest.
给我当帮手，留下来吧。
Favour me and stay.
我可要拿最高的薪水喔。
I get top fucking dollar.
珍,镇子里有新的酒吧了吗?
New saloon in the camp, Jane?
我知道那是个美妙的开场白
I know that's some clever opening gambit...
可以让我爽到爆。
to culminate in breaking my balls.
我只是在说我在检查平常那些
Just saying I checked the
包裹，在我离开前
usual spots 'cause I wanted to say goodbye...
因为我说声再见  以防你走了或者死了
before I left camp, so in case you go ahead and fucking die--
拜拜，查理，拜拜了您呐。去他妈的好好玩吧。
Goodbye, Charlie. Goodbye. Have a good fucking trip.
闭嘴吧你！
Shut the fuck up!
因为这就是会出现的， 当你回来的时候...
'Cause it so happens, when you return...
如果你没被弄死...
if no trees or animals killed you...
你又会疯了似的批评这个批评那个了
you were fucking driving crazy with criticism...
你会发现我早就离开这鬼地方了。
you'll find I've moved out of this shitbox.
所以我就不会再撅你 让你尴尬了
So I don't have to fucking embarrass you...
或是让你这样的世界上最丑
or fucking have you hovering over me...
保姆一样缠上我
Iike the ugliest fucking nurse in the fucking universe.
-去哪里 -什么去哪里
-lnto where? -lnto where what?
你要去哪里
Into where are you fucking
当你搬走的时候
moving when you fucking move out of here?
去那条路上的妓院
Into the fucking whorehouse down the way...
你把我送去照顾的那个女人在的那家
which you fucking sent me to see that woman at.
如果你一定要烦我
If needing to piss in my ear
那就不要说出来你脑中任何一个想法
didn't crowd out every other fucking thought...
或者回忆了
or recollection in your head!
你们两个相处的怎么样
How did the two of you get along?
我不是说我搬到那里了吗
Did I just fucking say I was moving in there?
那里是一个妓院意味着
Which being it's a fucking whorehouse could indicate...
一些讨厌的工作安排或是其他一些惹人厌的东西
some fucking business arrangement or some other fucking thing.
是的 我要成为女王般的妓女了
Yeah, I'm gonna be queen hooker.
查理  你就是瞎操心
You're a keen fucking student of the human scene, Charlie!
好
Well, good.
很好
Good.
不管怎样  你要去哪儿
Where are you going, anyway?
我已决定不告诉你
I've made a decision not to tell you.
如果你决定不告诉我
If you made a decision not to tell me,
那你刚刚和我说什么
what did you just fucking tell me for?
我的决定是不告诉你详细的目的地
My decision is not to tell you my specific destination.
因为
'Cause...
我觉得我不应该这么做
I don't think I should.
就是这样
And that's that.
好吧 预祝你这目的地不明的旅行安全
Well, have a safe journey to your unannounced destination...
能安全回来
and a safe fucking return.
希望你的新生活一切顺利
And good luck to you with your new living arrangement.
对斯塔布斯小姐表示敬意
And my best, please, to Miss Stubbs.
查理 你不仅仅蛋疼
And you not only a fucking pain in the balls, Charlie...
也是我遇到的最奇怪的人
but also the strangest fucking person I ever met.
你以后在这里不会有人和吵了
You'll get no argument here.
谢谢
Good!
3加3等于6
Three plus three would equal six.
我有时候算成九就是想自娱自乐
Well, I sometimes put nine to amuse myself.
好了 抬起来吧
All right, take it up.
他很仔细就像他爸爸
Vigilant to detail like his pa.
我认为盖勒特夫人作为银行的主要赞助人
I'd think Mrs Garret, as the bank's chief backer...
可能会想在开业时出现
might wish to be present for its opening.
-就这件事来说 我已经得到了她的委托
-Well, as far as that, I got her proxy.
-但是她真的会想这么做吗
-Yes, but wouldn't she wish to be?
或许她会的
Perhaps she would.
我可以问一下
I can ask.
打扰了
Excuse me.
事情进行的怎么样了？
What the fuck's going on?
你问错人了[埃尔斯沃斯会错意了]
You ask the wrong fella.
那两个女人简直势同水火
The water comes to a boil between them two fucking women...
我向你保证
I will fucking guarantee you that much.
你有向盖勒特夫人求婚吗  你发过誓你会的
Have you proposed to Mrs Garret as you fucking swore you would?
不要管我发没发誓
Leaving aside what I did swear or didn't,
我已经求过婚了
let's say I fucking have.
然后呢
And?
这就是问题所在 她没有说同不同意
That's where the matter stands. She ain't said yes or no.
那个女人倾向于同意还是不同意 埃尔斯沃斯
How did the lady incline, fucking Ellsworth?
我不想猜 崔克茜
I wouldn't guess, fucking Trixie.
你有表现得很热情吗
Did you present yourself enthusiastic?
如果你问的是这个  那么我没跳吉格舞表示热情
Well, I didn't dance a jig if that's what you're asking.
或是表现的很忧郁 让她拒绝了你
Or more fucking glum like, next to inviting refusal.
不忧郁
Not glum.
那就没让她倾向于拒绝了
Not inviting refusal.
我的方式很直截  我称之为
Straightforward, I'd call it.
-发自内心的 -是的
-Sincere? -Yeah.
那她又是怎么回事
Well, what the fuck is her fucking problem then?
你是一个很有潜力的候选人
You're a worthy enough fucking candidate...
把能给的都给了她
given all her fucking givens.
令人欣慰的认可
Warm endorsement.
她本应说明意愿的
She'd have to state her reservations.
盖勒特夫人给我写了一封信
Mrs Garret writ me a letter...
说她昨天是怎么和你发脾气的
saying how yesterday she lost her temper with you somewhat...
她倾向的判断 她意识到你是个平克顿
and judgement, she tipped she was on to you being a Pinkerton.
我就直说了
Being bright, I expect
你推测是我告诉的她
you concluded it was me must have told her.
意思就是我事情都告诉了她
Meaning maybe I sold over to her.
觉得我的忠诚有问题
And with my allegiance now in question...
我预料到你给私人侦探发了重要的东西
I expect you wired the Pinkerton big shots...
争论说你不应该签任何文件
arguing you oughtn't sign any documents...
这或许能够证明你 代理人
that might be able to prove that you, the agency...
并且盖勒特夫人在法律上雇佣了我
and Mrs Garret's fucking in-laws hired me...
让我杀死她丈夫并把尸体放在盖勒特夫人的门口
to lay at Mrs Garret's doorstep the murder of her husband.
还有 斯维尔根先生
And further, Mr Swearengen,
至于对你的支持的购买价格问题上
that as to purchase of your allegiance...
他们可能会希望公开出价
now in question they might wish to keep the bidding open.
出价一直都是公开的 伊斯林豪瑟小姐
Bidding's open always on everyone, Miss lsringhausen.
但是我希望你理解 知道我做的事
But I expect you understand, knowing as I do...
盖勒特应该放弃她的所有权
should Mrs Garret lose her claim,
而不是让他们自己来经营
rather than operate it themselves...
她的夫家会将其卖给第三方
her cunt in-laws will sell to third party cocksuckers inimical...
对于我在这儿的所有利益有敌意的第三方
to the whole of my interests in this camp!
买我的忠诚来对付我
To buy my allegiance against myself...
姻亲
in-law cunts...
白痴的经营者确实不得不出很高的价格
and shitheel operators would have to bid very high indeed.
不 更有可能的是 伊斯林豪瑟小姐
No, more likely, Miss lsringhausen,
我认为你已经考虑
I think you'd contemplate...
改变你的支持了 在我履行我的诺言之前
changing your allegiance before I would mine.
对我有什么好处
What benefit would I consider might accrue to me?
我把你白痴上司的消息拦下来给你
I intercepted your shitheel boss' message back to you...
通过电报机
through the miracle of telegraph,
这回答了那个的问题
and it answers that very question.
如果我得到消息 我会逐字读给你
As I have it here before me, I will read it to you verbatim.
伊斯林豪瑟小姐 这将会让你免受很大的痛苦
"Miss lsringhausen, as this will save you great pain...
并且可以让你免遭毒手
"And keep you from being killed...
在斯维尔根先生起草的所有文件上签字
"Sign all documents Mr Swearengen has drawn.
拿着这5000块 赶紧消失
"Take the $5,000 and disappear.
此致 你的老板 平克顿
"Yours sincerely, your boss, Pinkerton shitheels."
秘密电报中提到的这5000块
The $5,000 alluded to in the invisible telegram...
这笔钱能现在就支付么
can the money be produced?
当然
Without, of course,
但我想让警长布洛克在场
I would want the Sheriff present at my signature...
并且护送我离开
and as my escort from the camp.
我保证会为你准备齐全
I bet that can be arranged.
我不能泄露电报信息的秘密
I can't betray the confidence of messages.
你自己做不到的事就不要瞎保证 布拉萨诺夫
Don't guarantee what you'll never do, Blasanov.
想想看 让你站在火中
Not without imagining your feet stuck to the fire.
老大
Sir...
我是个父母双亡的人
I am a person whose parents have been murdered...
也没有其他的家庭成员可供挂念
and no other family connection and feeling...
守住信息的秘密就是我唯一的寄托
and believe in confidence of messages.
你说这些什么意思
What the fuck's all that supposed to mean?
我是说
I hope...
就算让我遭受火刑
feet in the fire...
也休想让我改主意
would not change me.
-恭喜你 纳托尔先生  -谢谢你 小盆友
-Congratulations, Mr Nuttall. -Thank you, young man.
你的自行车感觉怎么样    并不颠簸
-How's the boneshaker? -Un-shook.
一句小玩笑而已
Which would be a fib to say about me.
警长 我来
I've come, Sheriff...
看看昨天在我这儿发生的枪击案你调查得怎么样
to ask what you've learnt of the shooting yesterday in my place.
摩斯 曼纽尔说他哥哥意外意外杀死的自己
Mose Manuel said his brother killed himself by accident.
意外
By accident?
在摩斯卖出所有权的两小时之前
Two hours before Mose sells their claim...
查理说他们全是自己安排的后事
that Charlie said they'd worked theirselves...
入殓  股份  迅速的过户给了赫斯特集团
Iock, stock, and barrel to the Hearst interests?
没有人目击者 汤姆
There's no witnesses, Tom.
真令人心痛  在以我的名字命名的地方发生了手足相残
Hurtful, brother against brother in a joint that bears my name.
这是近来最痛心的消息
The most recent hurtful event.
内个 我可以让威廉姆协助我
But might I ask William to assist me...
校准自行车的车把吗
in calibrating the boneshaker's handlebars?
去吧 威廉姆
Go ahead, William.
先生 我不知道怎样校准车把呢
I don't know how to calibrate handlebars, sir.
噢 没那么难学 威廉
Oh, knowledge is overrated, William.
只要你肯下心思 多花点功夫
Diligence is what's required in the service of a willing spirit.
别紧张 别紧张 小子 我还要用右手倒水呢
Easy! Easy, boy. I use my right hand to pour.
然后布洛克夫人说
And then Mrs Bullock said...
既然它是你的 你可以看看安装好的保险箱
as it's yours, you might want to see the safe installed.
-真的  -是 夫人
-Did she? -Yes, ma'am.
保险箱及里面的钱运到的时候
Having brought the midday
她正好拿过来午饭
meal as the safe arrived with the money inside.
布洛克先生对他妻子说了些什么
And what did Mr Bullock say to Mrs Bullock?
他说那可是个好主意
He said that might be a good idea.
你描述的是和他当时的表现一样么  没加工吧
With enthusiasm equalling yours as you describe the moment?
我关于部落的部分所说的
I'd say on Mr Bullock's part...
大概是原汁原味的 盖勒特夫人 是的
about equal enthusiasm, Mrs Garret, yes.
-尽管布洛克太太依旧坚持他也没有什么别的表情？ -是的
-Despite which Mrs Bullock persisted?  -Yes.
哦 或许我不该让她失望
Well, perhaps I oughtn't to disappoint her.
之前我问过你的我们可能需要讨论的别的事
Earlier when I asked what else we might have to discuss...
我提及的我的求婚
I referred to my proposal.
当我当时明白了你的想法
I took that to be your meaning at the time.
你选择了不予答复
Chose not to respond.
是的 我没答复 因为我还没打定主意
Not to, yes, as I hadn't yet made up my mind.
-那现在呢  -还没有
-Have you now? -Nor have I now.
你要我在履约布洛克的邀请之前
Would you have me decide now,
就做出决定吗
before I act on Mrs Bullock's invitation?
你要将我置身这样的条件下么？
Do you put me to those terms?
好像 也没那么急
I guess there's no burning rush.
我们去散下步吧 索菲亚
Shall we go for a walk, Sofia?
你要不要跟我们一起吃点
Are you certain you won't join us?
谢谢
Thank you.
我一般不吃午饭
I tend to forego the midday meal.
我曾想过
It occurred to me...
不管怎样 盖勒特夫人有她出席的理由
Mrs Garret having reason to be present in any case...
我们或许可以用更开放的方式谈论
that we might discuss in more formed a fashion...
关于孩子们的教育计划
our plans for the children's schooling.
更有建设性的那种 比以前的谈话
More constructively than in some previous conversation.
我乐意
I'm delighted.
太好了
Wonderful.
斯维尔根先生要见你 警长
Mr Swearengen asked to see you, Sheriff.
这会儿不行
Not just now.
有人把绳子一边系在
A man tying the right rope to
架子上  另一边拴在乌云上
the frame and the other end to a thunderhead...
那样就能用机器拉着乌云跑了
could use the machine to tow clouds.
我再高点就好了
I wish I was taller.
嗯 等你腿再长点
Well, when your legs lengthen...
我猜你会成为
I calculate you will be
世界上最厉害的拖拽云朵的高手
among the great cloud haulers of the world.
就像你昨天骑得那样  纳托尔先生
Just to ride like you did yesterday, Mr Nuttall.
你当时应该看下你的表情的
You should have seen your face.
贝拉联盟的沟将是对我的考验 威廉
The Bella Union gap was my crucible, William.
但是却名不副实
The fabled mud slick.
我向前挪了下肩膀 只挪了一点点
I shifted shoulders forward, but not too much...
沿着雪橇的印记 ho
and at a sledgetrench, ho!
把屁股往左偏点  以上帝的名义
Swung my buttocks left, by God...
这样调转车把 砰
turned the bars just so, thump!
埋在路面下的木板  bom的一下
The buried plank, bom!
我不是通过了考验么？
And did I not come through a treat?
-下午好 -下午好
-Good afternoon. -Good afternoon.
-下午好 -下午好 盖勒特太太
-Good afternoon. -Good afternoon, Mrs Garret.
下午好 布洛克太太
Good afternoon, Mrs Bullock.
祝你投资顺利
Very good wishes on a venture
提供给营地里的人那么多机会
offering opportunity to so many in the camp.
-谢谢  -由衷
-Thank you. -Hope.
为了您承担起孩子们的教育大业
For taking up the education of the camp's children...
我的索菲亚加入  谢谢
my Sofia included, thank you.
我感觉我上次表示的不够明确
As I feel I expressed inadequately when last we spoke.
吃点么  盖勒特夫人
Bite of meat, Mrs Garret?
不  谢谢
No, thank you.
那个就是保险箱了
That appears to be the safe.
威廉姆
William...
敢挑战一下双人的？
do we dare ride double?
-你敢我就敢  -我敢
-I do if you do. -I do!
无谓的人们啊
Dauntless then!
鼓足勇气  向着至高的位置和荣誉冲啊
Courage high to the sticking place and honour bright...
我要爬上去蹬脚踏板  找个最适合的方法让你上来
as I mount and circle and consider the best way to swoop you up.
先生  在这等你了
Awaiting you here, sir.
漂亮
Great.
干得好
Beautiful.
看着很有条理
This all seems very much in order.
第一个存款人
First depositor.
就是见证个签字仪式  警长
It's to witness some wrist business, Sheriff.
Al说很简短但很重要
Al said brief but of crucial importance.
-要去多久？  -很短暂
-How long will we be? -Brief, very.
你帮我省了顿打
And you'd save me a beating.
抱歉了
Excuse me.
把脑袋放上面
Get your head on it.
-我头在上面了  -把你的头放上面  Tess
-My head is on it. -Get your head on it, Tess!
已经这么做了  托利维先生
It's on it, Mr Tolliver.
曼纽尔先生  听着像是满嘴了
It does sound like a girl with a mouthful, Mr Manuel.
上帝啊
Jesus Christ!
她把舌头伸在面颊上也能达到同样的效果
Her tongue in her cheek can achieve the same fucking effect.
我要和警长谈谈
I require a conversation with the sheriff.
供认一个罪犯
Confess a crime.
你在出千骗我
You're fucking cheating me!
-从下面滚开  -我没出千  先生
-Get the fuck out from under there! -I ain't cheating you, sir.
曼纽尔先生  给你换个庄家？
Will you have another dealer, Mr Manuel?
再来个老千？
Another fucking cheat?
赌博自古以来就是胜负难料的  先生
Hot and cold's the way the cards run, sir, time immemorial.
我想要回来
I want it back.
还给我
Give it back to me!
里昂 还给他最后的赌注  我们就认为那把没赌
Give him his last wager, Leon. We'll call that one no bet.
是的  先生  托利维先生
Yes, sir, Mr Tolliver.
所有的东西
All of it. Everything.
Now, 我认为你知道的  曼纽尔先生
Now, I can't do that, Mr Manuel,
我不能那么做
as I believe you know.
那些来福枪都指着你脑袋呢
And those rifles are aimed at your head.
一切
Everything!
曼纽尔先生 包括青春么？为什么不再漂亮点呢？
Including youth, Mr Manuel? And why not beauty?
也许不能真的恢复
Not credibly restored, perhaps,
但是可以作为一个不可协商的条款
but as a new non-negotiable term?
那你想不想让你兄弟查理活过来呢？
Would you not have, too, your brother Charlie resurrected?
你会保证你对他的嫉妒消失掉么？
Would you stipulate your envy of him be purged?
当然  你会坚持说查理有什么什么的缺点
Surely, you'll insist that Charlie retained certain defects.
他不可言喻的自欺欺人
His ineffable self-deceptions...
比如  指责就成了你生活的乐趣
for example, which were your joy in life to rebuke...
和目的  只要你真的有这种机会都会挽回了
and purpose, so far as you had one.
我想你会放弃那些
I suppose you would see removed
让你爱他的美好品质
those qualities which caused you to love him.
并且忽视了
And the obliviousness to
你杀了他这事儿的危险性
danger which allowed you to shed his blood.
我要和布洛克谈谈
I want to talk to Bullock!
去找医生
Get the fucking Doc!
我能平息这件事的
I could have cooled that out.
托利维先生  李能够在我的命令下烧了这个建筑
On my order, Mr Tolliver, Lee will burn this building...
在我让他烧之前  之中或者之后砍了你
mutilating you before, during or after as I specify...
又或者他随便选个我没禁止的时间
or when he chooses unless I forbid.
Oh  我唯你是从
Oh, my full attention is at your disposal.
在找医生之前先告诉警长这儿发生了什么
Tell Sheriff Bullock what transpired here before getting the Doc.
-现在是多少  -8
-And now how many? -Eight.
第四个分成了两部分
Two portions of four.
非常好  索菲亚
Very good, Sofia.
我可以得块糖么？
May I have candy?
索菲亚  你在为你的算数要奖品
You ask a reward, Sofia, for doing your numbers?
你从哪学来的？
Where would you get such an idea?
来自崔克茜
"Received from Trixie...."
那个妓女
The whore.
我可以签第一份收据么
May I sign the first receipt?
好的  请你来签字吧
Yes, please do.
-Huzzah.  -我找警长布洛克
-Huzzah. -I'm to fetch Sheriff Bullock.
他随时都会回来
He'll be back momentarily.
-好的  开始了  -准备  准备好么？
-All right, let's go. -Ready, ready?
-准备  开始  -上来  上来
-Ready. Here we go. -Up! Up!
我们错过了
We missed.
试验运行  平安无事  Hey  转过来 汤姆
Trial run. No harm done at all. Hey, swing around, Tom!
正转呢
On my way!
给腿绳打结
Tie off that leg rope.
你想像国家帮助你那样献身祖国么？
Don't you want to serve your country as good as they been to you?
我打赌你甚至都没投过票
I bet you don't even vote.
抓住腿绳
Hold that leg rope!
Whoa, hey, whoa!
这是我们之间的秘密 别告诉任何人
That's between us. Tell no one I give you that.
我还是不接受的好  但是好意领了
I'd best not, but thank you.
你守住这个秘密  你不会有麻烦的
You keep it a secret, and you won't get into any trouble.
如果你和你父亲在一起的时候
And if you told I helped you on the bike,
告诉他我帮你骑上的自行车
that's between you and your father.
Hey!
我感觉后背断了
I think my back's broke.
真爱字幕组招募群：
319832261